[{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664061504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":13772,"timeElapsed":62054},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664073777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":12272,"timeElapsed":74327},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664081749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7968,"timeElapsed":82298},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664087234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5484,"timeElapsed":87784},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664095171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":7935,"timeElapsed":95721},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664102903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":7729,"timeElapsed":103453},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664107713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4807,"timeElapsed":108263},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664112276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4561,"timeElapsed":112826},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664117924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5645,"timeElapsed":118474},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664126815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6631,"timeElapsed":127365},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664130927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4111,"timeElapsed":131477},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664138818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7889,"timeElapsed":139368},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664146830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8010,"timeElapsed":147380},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":39518,"timeElapsed":186900},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7240,"timeElapsed":194142},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664199275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5682,"timeElapsed":199825},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664203883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4606,"timeElapsed":204433},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3301,"timeElapsed":207736},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664218554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":10314,"timeElapsed":219104},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664226589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":8033,"timeElapsed":227138},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664233276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6685,"timeElapsed":233826},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664237489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4211,"timeElapsed":238039},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664243649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6159,"timeElapsed":244199},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2115,"timeElapsed":246315},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664248229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2463,"timeElapsed":248779},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664250938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2707,"timeElapsed":251488},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":253620},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":9425,"timeElapsed":264053},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4986,"timeElapsed":269041},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8020,"timeElapsed":277062},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5945,"timeElapsed":283009},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664286283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3821,"timeElapsed":286833},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3271,"timeElapsed":290105},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3085,"timeElapsed":293192},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664298513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5868,"timeElapsed":299063},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664301786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3271,"timeElapsed":302336},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5280,"timeElapsed":308634},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8984,"timeElapsed":317620},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664324255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7183,"timeElapsed":324805},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3357,"timeElapsed":328164},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":5413,"timeElapsed":333579},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664339003,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5972,"timeElapsed":339553},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":6754,"timeElapsed":346309},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664348447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2687,"timeElapsed":348997},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664352537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4088,"timeElapsed":353087},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5894,"timeElapsed":358982},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6444,"timeElapsed":366475},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664369500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3573,"timeElapsed":370050},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5623,"timeElapsed":375675},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1310,"timeElapsed":376988},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3956,"timeElapsed":380946},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2325,"timeElapsed":383273},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664385091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2366,"timeElapsed":385640},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664388788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3697,"timeElapsed":389338},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1815,"timeElapsed":391156},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7013,"timeElapsed":399104},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2740,"timeElapsed":401846},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664405397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4099,"timeElapsed":405946},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3797,"timeElapsed":409745},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412216,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3019,"timeElapsed":412765},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664416211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3994,"timeElapsed":416761},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664418332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":418882},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664421588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3254,"timeElapsed":422137},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664423871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2282,"timeElapsed":424421},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3197,"timeElapsed":427620},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664433147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5133,"timeElapsed":433697},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664437309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4160,"timeElapsed":437859},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7753,"timeElapsed":445614},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1501,"timeElapsed":447119},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664448736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2166,"timeElapsed":449286},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1526,"timeElapsed":450814},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664454379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4113,"timeElapsed":454929},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664457601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3220,"timeElapsed":458151},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664460045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2442,"timeElapsed":460595},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664468947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":8067,"timeElapsed":469497},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":472730},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664476366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4184,"timeElapsed":476916},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2169,"timeElapsed":479087},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664482049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":482599},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664483984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1933,"timeElapsed":484534},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664487267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3282,"timeElapsed":487817},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3606,"timeElapsed":491424},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":1913,"timeElapsed":493339},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664504215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":10360,"timeElapsed":504765},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664506452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2235,"timeElapsed":507002},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664510816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4362,"timeElapsed":511366},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2462,"timeElapsed":513829},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4793,"timeElapsed":518623},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2067,"timeElapsed":520692},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664523016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2872,"timeElapsed":523566},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664525101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2082,"timeElapsed":525650},{"subjectID":"8xdq2tgo9d","prolificID":"5c41c72864c45700016a1d17","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421551d14ecaf3c618ab8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664527631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2529,"timeElapsed":528181}]